♪ Ding dong ding ♪
♪ Have a holly, jolly Christmas ♪
♪ It's the best time of the year ♪
♪ I don't know if there'll be snow ♪
♪ But have a cup of cheer ♪
♪ Have a holly, jolly Christmas ♪
♪ And when you walk down the street ♪
♪ Say hello to friends you know ♪
♪ And everyone you meet ♪
♪ Oh, ho the mistletoe ♪
♪ Hung where you can see ♪
♪ Somebody waits for you ♪
♪ Kiss her once for me ♪
♪ Have a holly, jolly Christmas ♪
♪ And in case you didn't hear ♪
♪ Oh by golly have a
holly jolly Christmas ♪
♪ This year ♪
♪ Have a holly, jolly Christmas ♪
♪ It's the best time of the year ♪
♪ And when you walk down the street ♪
♪ Say hello to friends you know ♪
♪ And everyone you meet ♪
♪ Oh, ho the mistletoe ♪
♪ Hung where you can see ♪
♪ Somebody waits for you ♪
♪ Kiss her once for me ♪
♪ Have a holly, jolly Christmas ♪
♪ And in case you didn't hear ♪
♪ Oh by golly have a
holly jolly Christmas ♪
♪ This year ♪
♪ Ding dong ding dong ding dong ♪